[{"answer": "You don't need to know nothing else", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "White? Maybe it was my bedding dress. Describe it to me", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "How long has it been", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Eighteen years", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Me and that place... my daughter", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "It's all right by me...I cook at a restaurant in town. Sew a little on the sly...", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Glad to get a look at you. Last time I saw your mama, you were pushing out the front of her dress. She's a fine looking young lady, that place. Fine looking. Got her daddy's sweet face", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Knew him. Knew him well", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "that place", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You going to tell me it's all right with this child half out of her mind", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "..then you fold it over like this see. This here used to be where my brothers and me slept. I was always at the top", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I ain't so smart", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yes you are", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You don't go no more", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, I used to go to my friend. She'd teach us with songs how to spell and count", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No I...I had to stop going", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh!...I didn't know you were there", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Help what, honey", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What was you looking for when you came here", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Somebody tell you about this place", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well, that makes one of you in this world", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No. Not two", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "To see her face", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yes. that place", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Them the feet you running on? My Jesus my..", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "that place! Fool girl", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Am I in that place", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " I'm still in that place", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " that place. Get me some velvet. It's a store called my friend. I seen pictures and they have the prettiest velvet", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Farther than that place", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What's that all over your dress", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You got another baby waiting for you", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "He white, ain't he", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "How was he different", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "No, he didn't tell me no. She worked here ten years. If she worked another ten, ya think she would have made it? I pay him for her last years and in return he got you, me and three more coming.", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "That's just it. We was men because he said so. We was men because we was on his land. You think he be calling us men if we ever walked off his land", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yes Ma'am. Look like it", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "They don't need telling", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Love is or it isn't. Thin love ain't love at all...I did stop him. I took and put my babies where they'd be safe..", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "It worked", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well what", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "If I call them, and they come what on earth am I going to say to them", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "That's the last thing they took from me", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "What I have to do is get in my bed and lay down. I want to fix on something harmless in this world", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Somebody new there. A woman. Thought you might know who she is", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I know that place", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "You sure", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Might see anything at all at 124", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "What's any of that got to do with Paul D.", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "What's any of that got to do with Paul D.", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I run him off", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "He didn't know nothing. And nobody. Except her, from when they was at that place my friend was at", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Sure he knew her. Her boy my friend, too", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "WILL YOU STAY", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "I WILL NEVER LEAVE YOU AGAIN", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You don't know what I think", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "I want to work, Miss Lady", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "No. I mean work work", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Fine. But what would I do at night", "docId": "Beloved.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "In case of what", "qsentId": 62}]